I mean, people
have the absolute
right to believe,
but ideas don't
have the right
not to
be laughed
at, basically.
I wanna get
your take. Why
does being able
to laugh at
religion matter
in a
free society,
a pluralistic
society like
we have?
I think we
should be able
to laugh at
all ideas like
that, especially ones
where there
are people
in power,
people who claim
to have this
absolute truth to
life and the
secrets to
the afterlife
and all
that stuff.
So we have
to be mocking
stuff like that,
'cause it's not
proven. These
are just
ideas. These
are beliefs
that other
people have.
And so it's
not about tearing
them down necessarily,
but it is
about being like,
hold on. Wait,
you said
this? I
think that
thing's absurd.
It's the freedom
of speech on
both sides. They
can say their
piece, and I
can say mine
and criticize
it. And
I think
that's important.
Yeah, people have
the absolute right
to believe, but
ideas don't have
the right
not to
be laughed
at, basically.